Huh?
あれ?
It really suits you.
めっちゃ似合うじゃん
め っちゃ似合うじゃん
It looks good on you.
似合う似合うしちゃう
It's mine.
自分のやつだね
Please bring it.
持ってきてくれと
It's been a while.
久々にね
I can see it.
見えちゃう
It's dangerous.
危ないね
What are you doing today?
今日何してる?
Were you eating pasta wearing this outfit?
この服着てパスタ食ってたの?
Oh, was this it?
あ、これでしたの?
different.
違う
eye
め
You might be sweating.
っちゃ 汗かいてるかもしれない
I'm sweating so much.
めっちゃ汗かいてる
No, no, no.
ダメダメダメ
After walking.
歩いてから
Huh?
あれ?
It's a little white.
ちょっと白い
It's a 2cm skirt, right?
2センチ目のスカートでしょ?
No, no.
違う違う
I can barely see it.
もろ見えだ
It looks vague.
もろ見えだね
That's scary.
怖いね
I can see it.
見えちゃう
too scary
怖すぎ
Ru.
る
Ya ba.
や ば
Too cute.
可愛すぎる
great.
偉い
That's great.
偉いね
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
Looks like fun, right?
楽 しそうでしょ?
Chase?
チェイス?
amazing.
すごい
You've gotten better at it.
上手になったね
It's dangerous though.
やばいんだけど
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
That's amazing.
すごいね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
amazing.
すごい
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
Chase.
チェイス
It's completely filmed.
全然撮られてる
I didn't take a picture.
撮ってない
I didn't take any pictures.
全然撮ってない
I'm taking pictures.
撮ってるな
It suits you.
似合うね
Oh no.
やば
delicious.
美味しい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
feeling
気持
Good.
ち いい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
It's cute.
可愛いね
cute.
可愛い
Please let me go.
離してくれ
I'm just eating a cup.
一杯食べてるだけだよ
Feel good.
気持ちよく
That's a good thing.
いいことだよ
Hide for a while.
ちょっと隠れ
Please show me some details.
ちょっと詳細見せて
fault.
あ ら
Totally cute.
全然可愛い
strange.
おかしい
cute.
可愛い
Feel good.
気持ちよく
You're too good.
上手すぎるね
That's amazing.
すごいね
terrible.
やばい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm sleeping.
寝てる
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Go, go, go.
行く行く
Shall we go already?
もう行っちゃう?
Go, go, go.
行く行く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Oh my goodness.
や ばいね
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
Go, go, go.
行く行く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
No more.
もうダメ
comment
コメント
Take a look
を 御覧
Please come down!
下 さい!